Contact

0754461242 (Mobile) neacsu.andrei.ro@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/andreineacşu-935129196 (LinkedIn) www.upwork.com/o/profiles/users/ _~01dd3c1a4f9bd4f979/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

HTML
Web Development
Front-End Development

Certifications

Responsive Web Design

Andrei Neacşu

Customer Support Specialist

Bucharest Metropolitan Area

Summary

https://www.frontendmentor.io/profile/Xeotheosis

Proud winner of the Educational Enrichment for Romanian Children scholarship.

I am always on the lookout for the next opportunity of working in an industry where my professionalism, experience of working with clients and deep understanding of the English language can come in handy.

Experience

GES - Global Experience Specialists Customer Support Specialist January 2022 - Present (1 year 11 months) Sibiu, Romania

Qualitest

Junior Analyst

July 2020 - October 2021 (1 year 4 months)

Bucharest, Romania

Landing in the middle of a fast paced production team meant I have to track all the new features our developer team is implementing live almost on a daily basis, and make sure everything is running smoothly by keeping a close eye on any complaints or feedback received from our customers. This means we have to be informed at all times of any new updates and be comfortable juggling with all of them, especially if a problem arises and we have to deal with it quickly.

This is a crucial part of the project since it has a domino effect, delaying new potential features from being released should we miss any feedback or losing potential customers. If everything runs well (as it should!) the new feature gets greenlighted and can now be enjoyed by the entirety of our users.

I find that my role here trains my professionalism, capacity to work under pressure and diplomacy skills to the maximum, which I am sure will prove to be strong assets for the future.

Webhelp Romania Translation Account Manager November 2019 - February 2020 (4 months) Bucharest, Romania

The main tasks of a Translation Account Manager were simple and very well defined:

- -Receive the translation project from all the francophone companies our employer worked with (Ubisoft, Compagnie des Alpes, Orange to name a few)
- -Establish a deadline and budget depending on the size of the project and its importance
- -Be on the lookout for the best translators suited for the project, establish first contact and present them the opportunity to work with us
- -Deliver the project within the established timeframe, without any additional costs to our previously confirmed budget

Upwork
English Translator
April 2017 - November 2019 (2 years 8 months)
Bucharest. Romania

The stepping stone of my career was working as a Freelancer with English, a huge benefit which allowed me to interact with clients from an early age, learn how to negotiate and manage my own personal time and be prepared for more difficult tasks to come.

Learning the English language straight up from it's natives in Boston, New Hampshire and New York City, gratitude to the EERC scholarship I won, helped to set me apart from the competition, landing me more clients. With the experience I gathered copywriting, translating books, creating subtitles and many such tasks, I built an impressive portfolio of over 35 successfully completed projects with a 97% satisfaction rate, opening the door to greater challenges and bigger clientele.

My freelancer profile is public and I encourage you to visit it yourself https://www.upwork.com/o/profiles/users/~01dd3c1a4f9bd4f979/

Education

University of Bucharest translations and interpreting , Language Interpretation and Translation \cdot (2017 - 2020)